A Guide to the Papers of George Conoly Phillips, 1942-1978
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
Sub-series F: Miscellaneous. This sub-series includes handwritten and typed notes, as well as personal agreements for the 1950s.
Series VI: Writing and Speeches. This series consists of three sub-series: Sub-series A: Writing; Sub-series B: Speeches; and Sub-series C: Speech Notes and Annotated Source Materials.
Sub-series A: Writing. This sub-series contains writing, papers, and drafts by Conoly Phillips. Included are editorials on the role of higher education and on morals for the ODU Mace and Crown student newspaper; and student papers for business management courses at ODU. Materials date from 1976 to 1978.
Sub-series B: Speeches. This sub-series includes speeches and presentations made by Conoly Phillips as Norfolk City Councilman, as well as annotated speeches by other people. Topics include: Norfolk history; Norfolk redevelopment; and the Norfolk City budget.
Sub-series C: Speech Notes and Annotated Source Materials. This sub-series contains annotated source materials and notes for speeches, writings, and presentations by Conoly Phillips. Topics include: cities, integration, politics, and public schools. Materials date from the 1970s to the 1980s.
Series VII: Multimedia. This series contains multimedia materials, and is broken into the following sub-series: A: Audio Cassettes; B: Compact Discs; C: Floppy Discs; D: Reel Tapes; E. VHS and Betamax Tapes; and F: Photographs.
Sub-series A: Audio Cassettes. This sub-series contains audio cassettes related to Conoly Phillips 1978 Senate campaign and a "Men's Prayer Breakfast" speech by Conoly Phillips.
Sub-Series B: Compact Discs. This series contains compact discs containing computer data, including advertising spots for Conoly Phillips automotive business and an architecture dealership design tour.
Sub-series C: Floppy Discs. This sub-series contains floppy disks containing automotive and dealership logos.
Sub-series D: Reel Tapes. This sub-series contains reel tapes containing advertising spots for Conoly Phillips automotive business.
Sub-series E: VHS and Betamax Tapes. This sub-series contains VHS and Betamax tapes containing interviews and presentations from Conoly Phillips political career including his time on the Norfolk City Council and his 1978 bid for the U.S. Senate.
Sub-series F: Photographs. This sub-series contains photographs. Photos relate to all areas of Conoly Phillips’ life including: his automotive dealerships; his political career; his education and personal life; and his religious involvements. Materials date from the 1940s to the 1990s.
Series VIII: Artifacts. This series contains Conoly Phillips Lincoln-Mercury business card; a Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury license plate; and political buttons “Conoly Phillips for Council”, "Re-Elect U.S. Senator Robertson" and "Stovall Clerk of Circuit Court”
Series IX: Oversize. This series contains oversize scrapbooks, posters, photos, awards, and maps.
Contents List
- Auto Dealership
  - Advertising and Marketing
    - Advertisements - Meetings and Notes Dece. 1969 - Jan. 1963 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Advertising 1960s (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Advertising 1970 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Advertising 1971 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Advertising 1972 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Advertising 1973 (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Advertising 1974 (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Advertising 1990s (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Advertising undated (Box-folder 1:9)
    - Matthius and Redmond Advertising Agency -- Copies undated (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Matthius and Redmond Advertising Agency -- Misc. 1972-73 (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Miscellaneous Marketing 1970s (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Newspaper Ads 1960s - 1990s (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Yellow Pages 1970-72 (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury Merger Announcement 1999 (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Conoly Phillips Lincoln-Mercury Press Release June 10, 1997 (Box-folder 1:16)
    - "Turning a name into a commercial" (article on Phillips brothers) 1964 (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Auto and Japanese Production Data 1981 (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Ford Marketing Institute, 1971 Dealership Training Courses 1971 (Box-folder 1:19)
    - Marketing Locality Definitions 1996-97 (Box-folder 1:20)
    - Auto Show - Scope 1972 (Box-folder 1:21)
    - Basketball Hoop stakes 1973 (Box-folder 1:22)
    - Color of Christmas Seal Contest 1969 (Box-folder 1:23)
    - Freedom Lincoln Mercury Grand Opening 2000 (Box-folder 1:24)
    - Opening Gala, Jim Phillips List 1997 (Box-folder 1:25)
    - Retailer Awards 1964 (Box-folder 1:26)
    - Capri 1970-71 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Cougar -- Cougar Girl Coloring Book undated (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Daimler 1960 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Fiat 1959-63 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Lincoln 1968-72 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Mercury (not Capri) 1969-71 (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Presidential Limousine 1968 (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Rambler 1964 (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Rambler Data 1964-65 (Box-folder 2:9)
    - Rambler -- Rambler gram undated (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Finances
    - Appraisal: 4949 Virginia Beach Blvd, Virginia Beach, VA 1977 (Box-folder 2:11)
    - Appraisal: Novella Heights 1983 (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Appraisal Report: Conoly Phillips Planet Cars Dealership July 14, 1999 (Box-folder 2:13)
    - Appraisal Report: Two Vacant Parcels, Chesapeake, VA June 16, 1996 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Audit 1981 (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Audit 1982 (Box-folder 2:16)
    - Audit 1988 and 1989 (Box-folder 2:17)
    - Audit Audit 1990 and 1991 (Box-folder 2:18)
    - Audit 1991 and 1992 (Box-folder 2:19)
    - Audit 1994 and 1995 (Box-folder 2:20)
    - Audit 1995 and 1996 (Box-folder 2:21)
    - City Taxes and Licenses 1957-60 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - City Taxes and Licenses 1961-63 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - City Taxes and Licenses 1964-65 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - City Taxes and Licenses Miscellaneous (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Financial Statements 1957 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Financial Statements 1958 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Financial Statements 1959 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Financial Statements 1960 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Financial Statements 1961 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Financial Statements 1962 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Financial Statements 1963 (Box-folder 4:1)
    - Financial Statements 1964 (Box-folder 4:2)
    - Financial Statements 1965 (Box-folder 4:3)
    - Financial Statements 1966 (Box-folder 4:4)
    - Financial Statements 1967 (Box-folder 4:5)
    - Financial Statements 1968 (Box-folder 4:6)
    - Financial Statements 1969 (Box-folder 4:7)
    - Financial Statements 1970 (Box-folder 4:8)
    - Financial Statements 1971 (Box-folder 4:9)
    - Financial Statements 1972 (Box-folder 4:10)
    - Financial Statements 1973 (Box-folder 4:11)
    - Financial Statements 1974 (Box-folder 4:12)
    - Financial Statements 1975 (Box-folder 4:13)
    - Financial Statements 1976 (Box-folder 5:1)
    - Financial Statements 1977 (Box-folder 5:2)
    - Financial Statements 1978 (Box-folder 5:3)
    - Financial Statements 1979 (Box-folder 5:4)
    - Financial Statements 1980 (Box-folder 5:5)
    - Financial Statements 1981 (Box-folder 5:6)
    - Financial Statements 1982 (Box-folder 5:7)
    - Financial Statements 1983 (Box-folder 5:8)
    - Financial Statements 1984 (Box-folder 5:9)
    - Financial Statements 1985 (Box-folder 5:10)
    - Financial Statements 1986 (Box-folder 5:11)
    - Financial Statements 1987 (Box-folder 5:12)
    - Financial Statements 1988 (Box-folder 5:13)
    - Financial Statements 1989 (Box-folder 5:14)
    - Financial Statements 1990 (Box-folder 5:15)
    - Financial Statements 1991 (Box-folder 5:16)
    - Financial Statements 1992 (Box-folder 5:17)
    - Financial Statements 1993 (Box-folder 5:18)
    - Financial Statements 1994 (Box-folder 5:19)
    - Financial Statements 1995 (Box-folder 5:20)
    - Financial Statements 1996 (Box-folder 6:1)
    - Financial Statements 1997 (Box-folder 6:2)
    - Financial Statements Report December 31, 1994 and 1993 (Box-folder 6:3)
    - Financial Statements Report December 31, 1992 and 1991 (Box-folder 6:4)
    - Financial Statements Report December 31, 1991 and 1990 (Box-folder 6:5)
    - Automobile Physical Damage Insurance Classifications, Symbols, and Premium for New and Used Passenger Cars, Virginia 1965 (Box-folder 6:6)
    - Insurance Policy: Phillips, Charlotte F. 1991 (Box-folder 6:7)
    - Pilot Life Insurance Company 1964 (Box-folder 6:8)
    - Vehicle Service Contract Reimbursement 1981 (Box-folder 6:9)
    - Barton Station I 1980s-1990s (Box-folder 6:10)
    - Barton Station II 1990s (Box-folder 6:11)
    - Property Purchase: Chesapeake, VA 1973 (Box-folder 6:12)
    - Proposed Plan for Norview Avenue 1962 (Box-folder 6:13)
    - Real Estate Prospectus 1990 (Box-folder 6:14)
    - Cash Receipts Oct. 4, 1971 – Apr. 9, 1982 (Box-folder 6:15)
    - Receipts and Notes 1970s-1980s (Box-folder 6:16)
    - Sales Records I, Rambler June 1962 - April 1963 (Box-folder 7:1)
    - Sales Records II, Rambler May 1963 - December 1963 (Box-folder 7:2)
    - Sales Records III, Lincoln-Mercury Dec. 30, 1962 - Dec. 30, 1963 (Box-folder 7:3)
    - Settlement Statement with Deed of Trust, Military Highway, Chesapeake, VA 1985 (Box-folder 7:4)
    - Settlement Statement: O.W.L. Ltd. August 10, 1983 (Box-folder 7:5)
    - Settlement Statement: Dove Corporation December 1, 1989 (Box-folder 7:6)
    - Ford Motor Co. Stock Prospectus 1955 (Box-folder 7:7)
    - Initial Meeting of Stockholders of Automoville, Inc. March 26, 1957 (Box-folder 7:8)
    - Stock Certificates -- Phillips Bros. Lincoln-Mercury (Blank) undated (Box-folder 7:9)
    - Stock Certificates – Phillips Bros. Lincoln-Mercury 1964-65, 1972 (Box-folder 7:10)
    - Stock Certificates -- Conoly Phillips Lincoln Mercury 1996 (Box-folder 7:11)
    - Stock Transfer, Phillips Tire and Wheel 1982 (Box-folder 7:12)
    - Phillips Discount Tire Center Stock Certificates 1959-76 (Box-folder 7:13)
    - Commonwealth of Virginia Corporate Income Tax Returns 1959 - 60 (Box-folder 7:14)
    - State and Federal Income Tax Returns 1963- 65 (Box-folder 7:15)
    - Trend Control Board 1971 (Box-folder 7:16)
    - Trend Control Board 1974 (Box-folder 7:17)
    - Authorization to Borrow 1982 (Box-folder 7:18)
    - Auto Price Lists 1958-72 (Box-folder 7:19)
    - Checkbook 1956-57 (Box-folder 7:20)
    - Contributions -- Misc. 1969 - 72 (Box-folder 7:21)
    - Expense Accounts -- A/C 220 - (#360) 1973 (Box-folder 7:22)
    - Monthly Order Worksheets 1970 (Box-folder 7:23)
    - Note and Security Agreement, Virginia National Bank 1979 (Box-folder 7:24)
    - Radio Price Lists undated (Box-folder 7:25)
    - Resource Bank – Equipment Borrowings 1997 (Box-folder 7:26)
    - SBA Loan 1946, 1959, 1960 (Box-folder 7:27)
    - Travel and Miscellaneous 1970 (Box-folder 7:28)
  - Leases / Contracts / Agreements
    - Agreement: G. Conoly Phillips and Ronald C. Hush 1974 (Box-folder 8:1)
    - Agreement: G. Conoly Phillips and Tench Phillips December 1977 (Box-folder 8:2)
    - Articles of Partnership: Tench Phillips, Sr; Tench Phillips, Jr.; G. Conoly Phillips 1963 (Box-folder 8:3)
    - Conoly and Tench -- Personal I 1958-72 (Box-folder 8:4)
    - Conoly and Tench -- Personal II 1966-68 (Box-folder 8:5)
    - Conoly Phillips Leasing Corporation 1978-79 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Tenco 1963-77 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Building - Miscellaneous 1963-64, 1971-73 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Business Certificate 1959 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Car Wash Materials 1970 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Community Relations Ford 1970 - 72 (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Computerized Automotive Reporting Service Inc. 1970 (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Computerized Automotive Reporting Service Inc. 1971 - 74 (Box-folder 8:13)
    - Contracts 1957-75 (Box-folder 8:14)
    - Contract: LP Gas Consumer 1973 (Box-folder 8:15)
    - Contract: Suffolk Broadcasting Corp 1970 (Box-folder 8:16)
    - Creditor’s Group Life and Disability Insurance - Phillips Mercury Lincoln 1981 (Box-folder 8:17)
    - Customer Service -- Richmond District Ford Motor Company 1971 (Box-folder 8:18)
    - Dealership Agreement 1996 (Box-folder 8:19)
    - Dealer Tags -- Demos 1970 - 72 (Box-folder 8:20)
    - Deed of Easement 1997 (Box-folder 8:21)
    - Ford 1972 (Box-folder 8:22)
    - Ford Driver Education Program 1970 - 71 (Box-folder 8:23)
    - Ford Motor Company Dealer Life Plan 1972 (Box-folder 8:24)
    - Ford Motor Leasing / Fleet 1971 (Box-folder 8:25)
    - History Dealer Agreements 1957 - 63 (Box-folder 8:26)
    - Leases I 1950s - 1960s (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Leases II 1970s - 1980s (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Lincoln-Mercury District Office 1968 - 73 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Lincoln-Mercury Division Ford Motor Co. -- Not District Office 1968 - 73 (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Lincoln Sales and Service Agreement 1997 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Office Equipment and Maintenance 1968-73 (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Title Insurance: Phillips Brothers Automoville 1962 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Warrants: Against Forgers and Check Alterations 1978 - 80 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Wetlands Documents 1993 (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Personnel, Policies, Procedures, and Customer Relations
    - Application: MPI Testing Material 1971-72 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Award Trips 1984, 1986, 1996, 1998 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Award Jewelry 1998 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Care and Share Employee Newsletter 1994-99 (Box-folder 9:13)
    - Christmas Letters 1977, 1989, 1993, 1994, 1996 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Correspondence -- Customers October 1969 - November 1973 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Correspondence -- Public Relations April 1968 - November 1973 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Customer Relations 1972 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Dealership Procedures undated (Box-folder 9:18)
    - Dept. Heads -- Memos -- Job Description and Policy Sept. 1969 -- May 1971 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Dept. Heads -- Memos -- Job Description and Policy June -- August 1971 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Dept. Heads -- Memos -- Job Description and Policy Sept. 1971 -- Dec. 1973 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Dept. Sales Incentives 1969-76 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Employee Development undated (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Employee Handbook: Phillips Mercury-Lincoln undated (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Employees -- Phillips Mercury Lincoln 1970-73 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Employment Application undated (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Go, Inc. 1972-75 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - Labor Relations 1971 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Market Surveys 1963-64, 1972 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Meetings 1965, 1967, 1988 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Merchandising School 1952 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - Mission Statement: Conoly Phillips Lincoln-Mercury undated (Box-folder 10:14)
    - Notes: Managers in Action 1971 (Box-folder 10:15)
    - Notes: Training 1982-83 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Pension Plan undated (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Personnel Lists 1982-83 (Box-folder 10:18)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures 1965, 1973 (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Phillips Patter Oldsmobile: Newsletters 1971 – 72 (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Places that Make a Difference 1978 (Box-folder 10:21)
    - Resignations 1981-85 (Box-folder 10:22)
    - Resumes 1992 (Box-folder 10:23)
    - School: Dealership Training 1969-72 (Box-folder 10:24)
    - The Talon, Freedom Lincoln Mercury Newsletter November 1999 (Box-folder 10:25)
    - Automotive Trade Association of Virginia April 14, 1965 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Automotive Trade Association May 1968 - February 1972 (Box-folder 11:2)
    - Continental “100 Club” 1970s (Box-folder 11:3)
    - Lincoln-Mercury Dealer Association (LMDA) Southeast 1991 (Box-folder 11:4)
    - NADA (National Automobile Dealers Association) January 1969 - December 1971 (Box-folder 11:5)
    - NADA II January 1972 - January 1975 (Box-folder 11:6)
    - National Dealer Council 1972 (Box-folder 11:7)
    - Tidewater Automotive Dealers Association, Code of Regulations 1967 (Box-folder 11:8)
    - Tidewater Auto Dealers Association, Customer No. 42354 1963-72 (Box-folder 11:9)
    - Virginia Motor Vehicle Dealer Directory 1970 (Box-folder 11:10)
    - Virginia Motor Vehicle Dealer Directory 1971 (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box-folder 11:12)
    - Correspondence January 1973 -- April 1973 (Box-folder 11:13)
    - Correspondence May 1973 -- December 1973 (Box-folder 11:14)
    - Correspondence January 1974 -- July 1974 (Box-folder 11:15)
    - Correspondence August 1974 -- December 1974 (Box-folder 11:16)
    - Correspondence January 1975 -- April 1975 (Box-folder 11:17)
    - Correspondence May 1975 -- May 1976 (Box-folder 11:18)
    - Correspondence 1992-94 (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Correspondence 1997 (Box-folder 12:2)
    - Correspondence 1999 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 40 Year Achievement Award, G.C. Phillips 1999 (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Award -- Milestone '72 1972 (Box-folder 12:5)
    - Chairman’s Award 1991 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Dealer World magazines featuring Conoly Phillips 1989, 1997 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Ford Merchandising School Forum magazine featuring Conoly Phillips Jan.- Feb. 1956 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Magazines -- Newsletters: Subscriptions, etc. 1969-73 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 12:10)
    - Notes undated (Box-folder 12:11)
    - Phillips Bros. Lincoln-Mercury Postcard undated (Box-folder 12:12)
    - President’s Award, Presented by Ford Motor Company 1998 (Box-folder 12:13)
- Religious Activities
  - Churches
    - First Presbyterian Church 1950s - 1980s (Box-folder 12:14)
    - Other Churches 1970s - 1990s (Box-folder 12:15)
    - Church School 1960s - 1980s (Box-folder 12:16)
    - Church Work I 1960s (Box-folder 12:17)
    - Church Work II 1960s, 1980s (Box-folder 12:18)
  - Christian Correspondence
    - Christian Correspondence I 1969 - 72 (Box-folder 12:19)
    - Christian Correspondence II 1973 (Box-folder 12:20)
    - Christian Correspondence III 1978
    - Christian Correspondence IV 1983-89 (Box-folder 12:22)
    - Christian Correspondence V 2002 (Box-folder 12:23)
  - Evangelical Caucus
    - Evangelical Caucus I 1978-79 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - Evangelical Caucus II 1978-83 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - Evangelical Caucus III 1978-81 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Evangelical Caucus IV 1978-79 (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Evangelical Caucus V undated (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Evangelical Caucus VI 1978-80 (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Evangelical Caucus VII 1978-79 (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Index Cards: Evangelical Caucus Mailing List I undated (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Index Cards: Evangelical Caucus Mailing List II undated (Box-folder 15:1)
    - Index Cards: Evangelical Caucus Members undated (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Leadership Prayer Breakfast
    - Leadership Prayer Breakfast I 1978-01 (Box-folder 16:1)
    - Leadership Prayer Breakfast II 1980-88 (Box-folder 16:2)
    - Leadership Prayer Breakfast III 1986 (Box-folder 16:3)
    - Leadership Prayer Breakfast IV 1986-88 (Box-folder 16:4)
    - Leadership Prayer Breakfast V 1984-86 (Box-folder 16:5)
  - Newsletters, Articles, and Speech Materials
    - Articles undated (Box-folder 16:6)
    - Conoly Phillips – Speeches and Writing undated (Box-folder 16:7)
    - Notes undated (Box-folder 16:8)
    - Perspective 1971-92 (Box-folder 16:9)
    - Religious Articles undated (Box-folder 16:10)
    - Religious Notes / Speech Materials undated (Box-folder 16:11)
    - Secular Humanism and the Equal Rights Amendment circa 1980 (Box-folder 16:12)
    - Talk by G. Conoly Phillips circa late 1970s (Box-folder 16:13)
    - Barry Brown – Religious / Political Meetings undated (Box-folder 16:14)
    - Doulas Ship Tour 1978 (Box-folder 16:15)
    - Guidepost Program to School Teachers 1968-75 (Box-folder 16:16)
    - Jesus '78 1978 (Box-folder 16:17)
    - Lydia Fellowship 1988 (Box-folder 16:18)
    - Missionaries 1981-91 (Box-folder 16:19)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews 1974 (Box-folder 16:20)
    - Youth Program 1965 (Box-folder 16:21)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 16:22)
  - Televangelists
    - Billy Graham 1970s-80s (Box-folder 16:23)
    - Christian Broadcasting Network 1960s-80s (Box-folder 16:24)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship 1973 - 74 (Box-folder 16:25)
    - Prayer Petitions undated (Box-folder 16:26)
    - Proclaim Evangelistic Association 1960s - 1990s (Box-folder 16:27)
    - Regent University Board of Trustees 1991, 1994 (Box-folder 16:28)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 16:29)
- Community / Civic Memberships and Activities
  - Sub-series A: Better Business Bureau
    - Better Business Bureau -- Membership and Board Affairs I August 1969 - December 1971 (Box-folder 17:1)
    - Better Business Bureau -- Membership and Board Affairs II 1972 - 73 (Box-folder 17:2)
    - Better Business Bureau Minutes 1973 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Boy Scouts
    - Boy Scouts I 1968, 1976 (Box-folder 17:4)
    - Boy Scouts II 1967, 1969 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Chamber of Commerce
    - Chamber of Commerce 1969 - 73 (Box-folder 17:6)
    - Chamber of Commerce: National undated (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Sub-series D: Norfolk Symphony
    - Norfolk Symphony 1968 - 69 (Box-folder 17:8)
    - Norfolk Symphony Orchestra 1968 (Box-folder 17:9)
  - Rotary Club
    - Northside Norfolk Rotary Club 1960-73 (Box-folder 17:10)
    - Programs 1960s (Box-folder 17:11)
    - Rotary Talk March 1987 (Box-folder 17:12)
  - SPSA
    - SPSA 1995 (Box-folder 17:13)
    - SPSA 1996 (Box-folder 17:14)
    - SPSA 1997 I (Box-folder 17:15)
    - SPSA 1997 II (Box-folder 17:16)
    - SPSA 1998 (Box-folder 17:17)
    - SPSA 2000 (Box-folder 17:18)
  - United Community Fund
    - Award for Distinguished Service 1976 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Board 1970-73 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Budget 1972 (Box-folder 18:3)
    - Minutes 1970-73 (Box-folder 18:4)
    - UCF -- State Budget United Way of Va. 1973-75 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Union Mission
    - Union Mission Board of Directors March 1, 1990 (Box-folder 18:6)
    - Union Mission Programs undated (Box-folder 18:7)
  - United Drug Abuse Council
    - UDAC Organization 1973 (Box-folder 18:8)
    - UDAC Executive Committee 1972 - 73 (Box-folder 18:9)
    - UDAC General Information I December 1972 - June 1973 (Box-folder 18:10)
    - UDAC General Information II June 1973 - December 1973 (Box-folder 18:11)
    - UDAC General Information III (Board Members Kit -- UDAC, Norfolk, VA) 1973-74 (Box-folder 18:12)
    - UDAC Personnel 1973 (Box-folder 18:13)
    - UDAC Budget of Finance 1973 - 74 (Box-folder 18:14)
    - UDAC Committee Assignments 1973 (Box-folder 18:15)
    - UDAC -- Grant Review Committee 1973 (Box-folder 18:16)
    - UDAC -- Legislative Committee 1973 (Box-folder 18:17)
    - UDAC -- Project Review Chesapeake 1972 - 73 (Box-folder 18:18)
    - 1972 - 73 January 26, 1973 (Box-folder 18:19)
    - UDAC Education Committee 1973 (Box-folder 18:20)
    - UDAC -- SV/PDC (Southeastern Virginia Planning District Commission) 1973 (Box-folder 18:21)
    - UDAC T + R (Treatment and Rehabilitation) Committee 1973 (Box-folder 18:22)
    - UDAC -- VDACC (Virginia Drug Abuse Control Council) 1973 (Box-folder 18:23)
  - Miscellaneous
    - AD. Review Board (Tidewater Advertising Review Board) 1973-74 (Box-folder 19:1)
    - American Cancer Society Annual Meeting Sept. 19, 1979 (Box-folder 19:2)
    - Awards - miscellaneous 1960s, 1990s (Box-folder 19:3)
    - CBU - Epworth Camp 1981-82 (Box-folder 19:4)
    - Hampton Roads 5% Club 1980s-90s (Box-folder 19:5)
    - Harbor Club 1968-73 (Box-folder 19:6)
    - Kings Daughter Hospital 1968-73 (Box-folder 19:7)
    - Mallory Country Club 1964-70 (Box-folder 19:8)
    - Norfolk Junior Chamber of Commerce – Distinguished Service Award 1961 (Box-folder 19:9)
    - Organization Resignations 1967-70 (Box-folder 19:10)